A healthy lifestyle can be
more rewarding than you think.
With Manulife Vitality,
the more healthy
choices you make,
the more Vitality
PointsTM you’ll earn.
And the more points you earn,
the more rewards you can get.
Set and reach weekly,
monthly and annual goals
to save big on travel,
the latest in
wearable technology,
fitness club
memberships, and more.
Plus,
save money on your insurance.
Every little step towards
improving your health counts.
And we’re with you along the way.
Manulife Vitality gives you
the tools to get healthier
and the rewards for
reaching your goals.
Find out how to make every
little step count today,
at Manulife.ca/Vitality